Guide to the Kathleen Hanna Papers MSS.271
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Filing Cabinet Files
  - Le Tigre translations [1 of 2], undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Le Tigre translations [2 of 2] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Le Tigre Tours [1 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Le Tigre Tours [2 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Le Tigre Tours [3 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Le Tigre Tours [4 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Le Tigre Tours [5 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Le Tigre Tours [6 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Le Tigre Tours [7 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Le Tigre Tours [8 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Le Tigre Tours [9 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Le Tigre Tours [10 of 10], [2000-2005] (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Le Tigre Music Stuff [1 of 5], undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Le Tigre Music Stuff [2 of 5], undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Le Tigre Music Stuff [3 of 5], undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Le Tigre Music Stuff [4 of 5], undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Le Tigre Music Stuff [5 of 5], undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Le Tigre Press [1 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Le Tigre Press [2 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Le Tigre Press [3 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Le Tigre Press [4 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Le Tigre Press [5 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Le Tigre Press [6 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Le Tigre Press [7 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Le Tigre Press [8 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Le Tigre Press [9 of 9], [1999-2004] (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Le Tigre Memories [1 of 8], undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Le Tigre Memories [2 of 8], undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Le Tigre Memories [3 of 8], undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Le Tigre Memories [4 of 8], undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Le Tigre Memories [5 of 8], undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Le Tigre Memories [6 of 8], undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Le Tigre Memories [7 of 8], undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Le Tigre Memories [8 of 8], undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - [Le Tigre] Website Originals [1 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - [Le Tigre] Website Originals [2 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - [Le Tigre] Website Originals [3 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - [Le Tigre] Website Originals [4 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - [Le Tigre] Website Originals [5 of 6], undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - [Le Tigre] Website Originals [6 of 6] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [1 of 7], [1998-2001] (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [2 of 7], [1998-2001] (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [3 of 7], [1998-2001] (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [4 of 7], [1998-2001] (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [5 of 7], [1998-2001] (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [6 of 7], [1998-2001] (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [7 of 7] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], [1998-2001] (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - More Theses About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [1 of 9], undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - More Theses About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [2 of 9], undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - More Theses About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [3 of 9], undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - More These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [4 of 9], undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - More These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [5 of 9], undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - More These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [6 of 9], undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - More These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [7 of 9], undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - More These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [8 of 9], undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - More These About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work [9 of 9] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Fake Activism [Folder Removed from More Theses About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work] [1 of 2], [2001] (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Fake Activism [Folder Removed from More Theses About Riot Grrrl/Hanna's Work] [2 of 2] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], [2001] (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Business [1 of 6], [1993-2003] (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Business [2 of 6], [1993-2003] (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Business [3 of 6], [1993-2003] (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Business [4 of 6], [1993-2003] (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Business [5 of 6], [1993-2003] (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Business [6 of 6] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], [1993-2003] (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Financial- Business Equipment, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Financial- Car, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Financial- Records/Videos, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Financial [unlabeled 1], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Financial [cancelled checks and check register], [1997-1998] (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Financial- Postage/Freight, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Financial- Cables, Blank DATs, Strings, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Financial [unlabeled 2], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Financial- Enter. Bus. Meals, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Financial- Costumes/Makeup, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Financial- Medical, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Financial- Equipment [1 of 2], [1997] (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Financial- Equipment [2 of 2], [1997] (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Financial- Travel [1 of 2], [1997] (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Financial- Travel [2 of 2], [1997] (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Financial- Phone Bills, [1996-1997] (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Money and Radio Charts [1 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Money and Radio Charts [2 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Money and Radio Charts [3 of 3], undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Old Tax Stuff [1 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Old Tax Stuff [2 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Old Tax Stuff [3 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Old Tax Stuff [4 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Old Tax Stuff [5 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Old Tax Stuff [6 of 12] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Old Tax Stuff [7 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Old Tax Stuff [8 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Old Tax Stuff [9 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Old Tax Stuff [10 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Old Tax Stuff [11 of 12], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Old Tax Stuff [12 of 12] [Kathleen Hanna's Original Folder], [1994-1997] (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from Johanna Fateman to Kathleen Hanna [1 of 4], [1995-1998] (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence from Johanna Fateman to Kathleen Hanna [2 of 4], [1995-1998] (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence from Johanna Fateman to Kathleen Hanna [3 of 4], [1995-1998] (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from Johanna Fateman to Kathleen Hanna [4 of 4], [1995-1998] (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Black metal filing cabinet with stickers, Undated; 271.2.0001; 1 item one filing cabinet (Object ID: 271.2.0001)
    General
    Dimensions: 297/8 x 181/4 x 261/2 inches
    filing cabinets.
- Series II: Photo Binders
  This series consists of photographs and negatives, mainly from 1987-1991, including work by Hanna.
  - [Binder of photos and negatives including] fashion, Hot Springs, Copystand-88, Alison/Doll Fountain, SElF Pub. shots, Fashion Show, Jon Marco-n-me, Viva K in LA, Fitz of Depression, Matt, Girl/boy cover, Allison's in Chicago, self portraits high school, [1987-1990] (Box 12)
  - [Binder of photos and negatives including] Kurt and Tracy, Giant Henry, Go-Team, Seattle/OK Hotel, Mecca Normal, Dead Mikey, Fitz of Depression, Slut Porn Girl, [1989-1991] (Box 13)
- Series III: Media
  This series contains VHS cassettes, 1/4" audio reels, mini digital video cassettes, CD-Rs and DVD-Rs, mostly documenting performances and studio recordings by Viva Knievel, Bikini Kill, Le Tigre and Julie Ruin.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access is limited to Subseries A: Video - Access Copies.
  - Subseries A: Video - Access Copies
    Access copies are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 1 of 5], 1989-92 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0038)
      Format: DVD
      TRT: 00:56:00
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 2 of 5], 1989-92 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0041)
      TRT: 01:31:00
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 3 of 5], 1989-92 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0044)
      TRT: 01:22:00
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 4 of 5], 1989-92 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0047)
      TRT: 01:29:00
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 5 of 5], 1989-92 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0050)
      TRT: 00:50:00
    - [1]-- Bikini Kill (Supreme Court/2 camera) [2]-- Tsunami/Fort Reno 8/92 [3]-- Bratmobile (NYC 5/92) [4]-- L7 (dc 4/92) [5]-- NOU [Nation of Ulysses] (DC 2/15/91) and "Truth or Dare"!, 1991-92 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0035)
      TRT: 02:02:00
    - Concert at Pink's Garage, Music: BIKINI KILL with Big Electric Cat & MC Frumpy; Electric Cats, MC Frumpy & Bikini Kill 3/1/92, 1992 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0053)
      TRT: 01:47:00
    - Bikini Kill 10/10/94 - Funk Shop, Ft. Collins Co., 1994 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0056)
      TRT: 00:31:00
    - Bikini Kill, Haltam City, TX 11/12/94, 1994 (Box Shared Fales 137, Dvd 271.0059)
      TRT: 00:43:00
    - [1] Bikini Kill - DAT '95 [2] Portland 11/5/95 [3] Roseland [4] S.F. 11/8/95 [5] Warfield 11/7/95 [6] AKE (maybe) Seattle '95, 1995 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0062)
      TRT: 01:37:00
    - Bikini Kill - Portland Roseland - 11/5/95 DAT, S.F. The Warfield 11/8/95 DAT, Sonic Youth - Seattle Paramount Theater 11/3/95, 1995 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0065)
      TRT: 02:03:00
    - Roesanne/Kathleen 11/14/95, 1995 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0067)
      TRT: 00:13:00
    - The Judy Spots, Sadie Benning, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0070)
      TRT: 01:13:00
    - Getting Close to Nothing, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0073)
    - Stupid Punx, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0076)
      TRT: 00:34:00
    - Riot Grrrl NYC, Abby Moser, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0079)
    - Le Tigre, Metro Daily Beat, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0082)
      TRT: 00:54:00
    - Girl Speak - at UC Irvine - Video by Film At Eleven, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0085)
      TRT: 00:30:00
    - Geffen Music Video; Sonic Youth "Bull In The Heather"; TRT 3:03; DGC Records, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0087)
      TRT: 00:03:00
    - 1) Viva Knievel "Good Girl Bad Dog, 2) 1200 Seconds, 3) Slim Moon "Poor Man's Parnassus", undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0090)
      TRT: 00:26:00
    - Bikini Kill, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0093)
      TRT: 00:32:00
    - Dub B-K, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0096)
    - A video by Corin Tucker with Bikini Kill; This special copy of a Revolution Girlstyle Now! Video was made with love for Toby, Kathleen, and Cathy (and Billy) from Corin, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0099)
      TRT: 00:17:00
    - 5/9 Guilty; Bikini Kill, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0102)
    - A Show of Appreciation for: Johanna, JD, and Kathleen; The X-Ray on the left shows a normal heart. On the right, the heart is enlarged., undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0105)
      TRT: 00:28:00
    - Kathleen MTV News, undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0108)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ/A 11, Undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0149)
      TRT: 01:02:33
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ 12, Undated (Box 18, Dvd 271.0150)
      TRT: 00:22:16
    - LT [Le Tigre] 2005 9:30 Club DC (Box 18, Dvd 271.0151)
      TRT: 01:03:32
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 - Sony 1 - Amsterdam (Box 18, Dvd 271.0152)
      TRT: 00:46:14
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 - Sony 2 - Gothenburg, SE (Box 18, Dvd 271.0153)
      TRT: 00:44:38
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 1 - Behind-the-scenes- Amsterdam, Hamburg, Conan O'Brien (Box 18, Dvd 271.0154)
      TRT: 00:46:35
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 2 - Amsterdam - Paradise Show (Box 18, Dvd 271.0155)
      TRT: 01:01:00
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 3 - Fabrik Hamburg, G (Box 18, Dvd 271.0156)
      TRT: 01:02:22
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 4 - Tragdam Festival; Gothenborg, Sweden (Box 18, Dvd 271.0157)
      TRT: 00:56:39
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 6 - 4.11.05 Copenhagen, D L: Camera R: Mono board mix (Box 18, Dvd 271.0159)
      TRT: 01:05:56
    - LT [Le Tigre] Euro 2005 7 - 4.13 Berlin, G Club M (Box 18, Dvd 271.0160)
      TRT: 01:04:01
    - LT [Le Tigre] Summ[mer] '05 1 - Gravy Train Bus, Bus Dance Party! (LA), Plant, Showers, McRorie, 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0161)
      TRT: 00:36:08
    - LT [Le Tigre] SUM '05 2 - Bugs!, JD Pose w/ car, JD drunk, Feminist Parking Lot! (In), 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0162)
      TRT: 00:43:45
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 3 - 8.4.2011 Exit/In Nashville, TN, L: Board, R: Mic, SR Pos, 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0163)
      TRT: 01:02:49
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 4 - Fem Park Lot Pt. II (IN), 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0164)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 5 9.6.05 Peabody's, Clev, Ohio. Board Mix Only Center Pos., 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0165)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Sum[mer] '05 6 - Chicago Show, 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0166)
    - Le Tigre - 9/18/05 Crowd interviews, Webster Hall, NYC, 24p camera, 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0167)
    - Le Tigre 9/18/05 Line @ Webster Hall, 2005 (Box 18, Dvd 271.0168)
    - Le Tigre 9/18/05 Le Tigre - Webster Hall, F.O.H. - Topiary, 2005 (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0169)
    - LT [Le Tigre] 9/18/05 Web Hall - Bob -, 2005 (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0170)
    - Le Tigre Webster Hall 9/18/05 (wide shot), 2005 (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0171)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Operation Peace, [2005] (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0173)
    - Le Tigre Tour 2004 - Mostow, Sweden, Germany, Slovenia, Paris (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0220)
      TRT: 00:59:26
    - Le Tigre Tour 2004 - Amsterdam, Irving Plaza, KCRW (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0221)
      TRT: 00:59:12
    - Le Tigre Tour 2004 (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0222)
      TRT: 01:00:00
    - Le Tigre Japan Sony 1 Kyoto (stage), Money Mark (stage), undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0223)
    - Le Tigre Japan Sony 2 - DVO SR, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0224)
    - Le Tigre Japan Sony 3 (stage angle) Budakon Plus, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0225)
    - Le Tigre Japan 2005 - 1 (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0226)
    - Le Tigre Japan 2005 - 2 (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0227)
    - Le Tigre Japan 2005 3 - LT, Mark - DUO, LT (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0228)
    - Le Tigre Japan 2005 4 - Duo (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0229)
    - Le Tigre Japan 2005 5 - Universal Records Interview (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0230)
    - Le Tigre Japan 6 - Budakon!, etc., undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0231)
    - Le Tigre Japan 7 - Nagoya, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0232)
    - Le Tigre Japan 8 -Tokyo Press, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0233)
    - Le Tigre NZ 2005 1 - Radio Interviews, etc. (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0234)
    - Le Tigre NZ 2 - Press/TV - Top of the Pops, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0235)
      TRT: 00:45:00
    - Le Tigre NZ 3 - King's Arun Show (board mix), undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0236)
    - Le Tigre NZ 4 - Big Day Out!, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0237)
    - Le Tigre NZ+A 5 - BigDay Out ANTICS!, etc., undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0238)
    - Le Tigre NZ/A 6 - BDO Sydney, Timelapse D.R., undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0239)
    - Le Tigre NZ/A 7 - Hotel Room, etc., undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0240)
    - Le Tigre NZ / A 8 - Gaelic Club - Crowd, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0241)
    - Le Tigre NZ / A 9 - Gaelic Club, Sydney, undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0242)
    - Le Tigre NZ/A 10 - Russ Interview w/LT, Gym workout, etc., undated (Box Shared Fales 138, Dvd 271.0243)
  - Subseries B: Video - Originals
    Original media is not available for use.
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 1 of 5], 1989-92 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0002)
      Format: VHS
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 2 of 5], 1989-92 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0002)
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 3 of 5], 1989-92 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0002)
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 4 of 5], 1989-92 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0002)
    - BIKINI GIRL - live (DC space 6/27/91), IPU 8/21/91, Prochoice 4/3/92, Wetlands 5/3/92, House of Ruth 5/29/92, Supreme Court 7/25/92 (two vers.),FUGAZI Whitehouse 1/12/91, PF Profile (91), NOU 2/15/91, FUGAZI homeless benefit 12/29/89 *For Kathy and BK - thanks for the inspiration! - Mark Andersen [Part 5 of 5], 1989-92 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0002)
    - [1]-- Bikini Kill (Supreme Court/2 camera) [2]-- Tsunami/Fort Reno 8/92 [3]-- Bratmobile (NYC 5/92) [4]-- l7 (dc 4/92) [5]-- Nov (DC 2/15/91) and "Truth or Dare"!, 1991-92 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0001)
    - Concert at Pink's Garage, Music: BIKINI KILL with Big Electric Cat & MC Frumpy; Electric Cats, MC Frumpy & Bikini Kill 3/1/92, 1992 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0003)
    - Bikini Kill 10/10/94 - Funk Shop, Ft. Collins Co., 1994 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0005)
    - Bikini Kill, Haltam City, TX 11/12/94, 1994 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0006)
    - [1] Bikini Kill - DAT '95 [2] Portland 11/5/95 [3] Roseland [4] S.F. 11/8/95 [5] Warfield 11/7/95 [6] AKE (maybe) Seattle '95, 1995 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0007)
    - Bikini Kill - Portland Roseland - 11/5/95 DAT, S.F. The Warfield 11/8/95 DAT, Sonic Youth - Seattle Paramount Theater 11/3/95, 1995 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0008)
    - Roesanne/Kathleen 11/14/95, 1995 (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0009)
    - The Judy Spots, Sadie Benning, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0010)
    - Getting Close to Nothing, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0018)
    - Stupid Punx, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0019)
    - Riot Grrrl NYC, Abby Moser, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0020)
    - Le Tigre, Metro Daily Beat, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0023)
    - Girl Speak - at UC Irvine - Video by Film At Eleven, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0024)
    - Geffen Music Video; Sonic Youth "Bull In The Heather"; TRT 3:03; DGC Records, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0025)
    - 1) Viva Knievel "Good Girl Bad Dog, 2) 1200 Seconds, 3) Slim Moon "Poor Man's Parnassus", undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0026)
    - Bikini Kill, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0027)
    - Dub B-K, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0028)
    - A video by Corin Tucker with Bikini Kill; This special copy of a Revolution Girlstyle Now! Video was made with love for Toby, Kathleen, and Cathy (and Billy) from Corin, undated (Box 17, Vhs ID: 271.0029)
      Related Materials
      This video is also present in the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers (see video 157.0282).
      Custodial History
      This video is missing as of March 2025.
    - 5/9 Guilty; Bikini Kill, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0030)
    - A Show of Appreciation for: Johanna, JD, and Kathleen; The X-Ray on the left shows a normal heart. On the right, the heart is enlarged., undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0031)
    - Kathleen MTV News, undated (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0032)
    - Le Tigre Tour 2004 - Mostow, Sweden, Germany, Slovenia, Paris (Box 17, Media ID: 271.0124)
      Format: MiniDV
    - Le Tigre Tour 2004 - Amsterdam, Irving Plaza, KCRW (Box 15, Media 271.0125)
    - Le Tigre Tour 2004 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0126)
    - Le Tigre Paris Café de la Danse 10/10/04, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0127)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan Sony 1 Kyoto (stage), Money Mark (stage), undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0128)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan Sony 2 - DVO SR, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0129)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan Sony 3 (stage angle) Budakon Plus, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0130)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 2005 1 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0131)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 2005 2 (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0132)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 2005 3 - LT, Mark - DUO, LT (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0133)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 2005 4 - Duo (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0134)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 2005 5 - Universal Records Interview (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0135)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 6 - Budakon! (Fott Angle), Press/Photo, (*Info Outfits), undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0136)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 7 - Nagoya, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0137)
    - LT [Le Tigre] Japan 8 -Tokyo Press, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0138)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ 2005 1 - Radio Interviews, TV Interviews, Top of the Pops (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0139)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ 2 - Press/TV - Top of the Pops - 40:00, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0140)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ 3 - King's Arun Show (board mix), undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0141)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ 4 - Big Day Out!, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0142)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ+A 5 - BigDay Out ANTICS!, Slipknot, Brisbane Zoo, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0143)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ/A 6 - BDO Sydney, Timelapse D.R., undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0144)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ/A 7 - Hotel Room - Horror Night, Hatebreed Talk - Horror Night, Gaelic Club Sydney Pre & Post Show, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0145)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ / A 8 - Gaelic Club - Crowd, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0146)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ / A 9 - Gaelic Club, Sydney, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0147)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ/A 10 - Russ Interview w/LT, Gym workout, Ross Angles, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0148)
    - LT [Le Tigre] NZ/A 11, undated (Box 15, Media ID: 271.0149)